Guide to the Scott Green Collection of Comics-Related Publications
Scott Green Collection of Comics-Related Publications
1975-2005
1975 2005
Green Scott E.
RBC 00008
The Scott Green Collection of Comics-Related Publications includes magazines and other publications about comics and comics collecting, as well as assorted mailings from the amateur press association I-SAPA.
Poet and journalist Scott E. Green has been an active writer in a number of fields including speculative poetry. Green’s publications include his Contemporary Science Fiction, Fantasy, and Horror Poetry: A Resource Guide and Biographical Directory and Isaac Asimov: An Annotated Bibliography of the Asimov Collection at Boston University. His poetry has been published in numerous print and web publications including Aeon, Amazing, Astropoetica, Space and Time, Star*Line, Strange Horizons, and Writer’s Journal.
1.5 linear feet
North Carolina State University Libraries, Special Collections Research Center
Donated by Scott E. Green
This collection is not fully processed. It is arranged with publication titles in alphabetical order.
Poet and journalist Scott E. Green earned his B.A. at Bates College in Asian history with a minor in government, and his M.A. in American history with a concentration in archives and museum management from Rhode Island College. Poet and journalist Scott E. Green has been an active writer in a number of fields including speculative poetry. Green’s publications include his Contemporary Science Fiction, Fantasy, and Horror Poetry: A Resource Guide and Biographical Directory and Isaac Asimov: An Annotated Bibliography of the Asimov Collection at Boston University. His poetry has been published in numerous print and web publications including Aeon, Amazing, Astropoetica, Space and Time, Star*Line, Strange Horizons, and Writer’s Journal. Green served as president of the Science Fiction Poetry Association, served the National Writers Union in a variety of capacities, and maintained membership in the Science Fiction and Fantasy Writers of America.
The Scott Green Collection of Comics-Related Publications includes magazines and other publications about comics and comics collecting, as well as assorted mailings from the amateur press association I-SAPA.
Green Scott E.; Green Scott E.; United States Comic books, strips, etc.
- Alter Ego, 2003, 2005 (Carton 1)
- Amazing Heroes, 1981 (Carton 1)
- American Book Collector Special Sherlock Holmes Issue, 1975 (Carton 1)
- Art? Alternatives (Carton 1)
- Back Issue The Ultimate Comics Experience, 2003-2005 (Carton 1)
- Busted! The Newsletter of the Comic Book Legal Defense Fund, 1995, 2000 (Carton 1)
- Cartoon Quarterly, 1988 (Carton 1)
- Comic Book Artist, 1975 (Carton 1)
- Comic Book Marketplace, 1991-2005 (Carton 1)
- Comic Relief, 1989 (Carton 1)
- Comic Times, 1980 (Carton 1)
- Comics Buyers Guide, 2005 (Carton 1)
- Comics Enquirer (a parody of a comics investment guide), 1992 (Carton 1)
- Comics Feature (Carton 1)
- Comics Journal, 1984, 1989 (Carton 1)
- Comics Review, 1984 (Carton 1)
- Comics Review Annual, 1987 (Carton 1)
- Comics Scene, 1982 (Carton 1)
- Damage (Carton 1)
- Danny Fingeroth's Write Now Magazine, 2002 (Carton 1)
- Darc Tangent, 1982 (Carton 1)
- FantaCo's Chronicles Series, 1983 (Carton 1)
- Fantazia, 1991 (Carton 1)
- Five Cents' Worth (Carton 1)
- Four Color Magazine, 1986 (Carton 1)
- Graphic Story Magazine, 1973 (Carton 1)
- Graphic Story Monthly, 1988 (Carton 1)
- I-SAPA mailings, c. 1975 (Carton 1)
- Interview, 1985 (Carton 1)
- Investors Newsletter, 1979 (Carton 1)
- Mangajin no. 14, 1992 (Carton 1)
- Nemo: The Classic Comics Library, 1984 (Carton 1)
- Newstime, 1993 (Carton 1)
- Nog, 2002 (Carton 1)
- Oracle, 1986 (Carton 1)
- Poetry Comics, 1981 (Carton 1)
- Pure Images, c. 1990 (Carton 1)
- Rubber Blanket, 1991 (Carton 1)
- Scandal Sheet, 1991 (Carton 1)
- Swashbucklers, 1980 (Carton 1)
- The Collector: The Journal of Media and Popular Culture, 1993 (Carton 1)
- The Comicist, 1989-1990 (Carton 1)
- The Comics Buyer's Guide, 1984 (Carton 1)
- The Funnies Paper Comic Strip Fanzine, 1984 (Carton 1)
- Thwak: It's America's Favorite Humor Magazine - They Just Don't Know It Yet!, 2001 (Carton 1)
- Trajectories, 1987 (Carton 1)
- Twilight Guild Ashcan, 1997 (Carton 1)
- Vintage Collectibles, 1985 (Carton 1)
- Wildcat: Tomorrow's New Stars of Art and Story, 1980 (Carton 1)
- Wizard: The Guide to Comics, 1991 (Carton 1)